Kiroween (the ôHackathonö) Official Rules
NO PURCHASE OR PAYMENT NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE OR PAYMENT WILL NOT INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING.á
SUBMISSION OF ANY ENTRY CONSTITUTES AGREEMENT TO THESE OFFICIAL RULES AS A CONTRACT BETWEEN ENTRANT (AND EACH INDIVIDUAL MEMBER OF ENTRANT), THE HACKATHON SPONSOR, AND DEVPOST.
á
1. Dates and Timing
Submission Period:áFriday, October 31, 2025 (8:30 am Pacific Time) û Friday, December 5, 2025 (2:00 pm Pacific Time) (ôSubmission Periodö).
Judging Period:áMonday, December 15, 2025 (1:00 pm Pacific Time) û Monday, January 12, 2026 (1:00 pm Pacific Time) (ôJudging Periodö).
Winners Announced:áOn or around Friday, January 30, 2026 (9:00 am Pacific Time).
á
2. Sponsor and Administrator
Sponsor:áAmazon Web Services, 410 Terry Avenue North, Seattle, Washington 98109 United States
Administrator:áDevpost, Inc. (ôDevpostö), 222 Broadway, Floor 19, New York, NY 10038
á
3. Eligibility
The Hackathon IS open to:á
Individuals who are at least the age of majority where they reside as of the time of entry (ôEligible Individualsö);
Teams of Eligible Individuals, maximum 3 participants per team (ôTeamsö); and
Organizations (including corporations, not-for-profit corporations and other nonprofit organizations, limited liability companies, partnerships, and other legal entities) that exist and have been organized or incorporated at the time of entry.
(the above are collectively, ôEntrantsö)
An Eligible Individual may join more than one Team or Organization and an Eligible Individual who is part of a Team or Organization may also enter the Hackathon on an individual basis.áIf a Team or Organization is entering the Hackathon, they must appoint and authorize one individual (the ôRepresentativeö) to represent, act, and enter a Submission, on their behalf. By entering a Submission on behalf of a Team or Organization you represent and warrant that you are the Representative authorized to act on behalf of your Team or Organization.
The Hackathon IS NOT open to:á
Individuals who are residents of, or Organizations domiciled in, a country, state, province or territory where the laws of the United States or local law prohibits participating or receiving a prize in the Hackathon (including, but not limited to, Brazil, Quebec, Russia, Crimea, Cuba, Iran, North Korea, Syria and any other country designated by the United States Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control)á
Organizations involved with the design, production, paid promotion, execution, or distribution of the Hackathon, including the Sponsor and Administrator (ôPromotion Entitiesö).
Employees, representatives and agents** of such Promotion Entities, and all members of their immediate family or household*
Any other individual involved with the design, production, promotion, execution, or distribution of the Hackathon, and each member of their immediate family or household*
Any Judge (defined below), or company or individual that employs a Judge
Any parent company, subsidiary, or other affiliate*** of any organization described above
Any other individual or organization whose participation in the Hackathon would create, in the sole discretion of the Sponsor and/or Administrator, a real or apparent conflict of interestá
*The members of an individualÆs immediate family include the individualÆs spouse, children and stepchildren, parents and stepparents, and siblings and stepsiblings. The members of an individualÆs household include any other person that shares the same residence as the individual for at least three (3) months out of the year.á
**Agents includeáindividuals or organizations that in creating a Submission to the Hackathon, are acting on behalf of, and at the direction of, aáPromotion Entity through a contractual or similar relationship.
***An affiliate is:á(a) an organization that is under common control, sharing a common majority orácontrolling owner, or common management; or (b) anáorganization that has a substantial ownership in, or is substantially owned by the other organization.
á
4. How To Enter
Entrants may enter by visiting kiro.devpost.com (ôHackathon Websiteö) and following the below steps:
Register for the Hackathon on the Hackathon Website by clicking the ôJoin Hackathonö button. To complete registration, sign up to create a free Devpost account, or log in with an existing Devpost account. This will enable you to receive important updates and to create your Submission.
Entrants will obtain access to the required developer tools/platform and complete a Project described below in Project Requirements. Use of the developer tools will be subject to the license agreement related thereto. Entry in the Hackathon constitutes consent for the Sponsor and Devpost to collect and maintain an entrantÆs personal information for the purpose of operating and publicizing the Hackathon.
Participants will be provided with the equivalent of the Kiro Pro+ paid plan for the duration of their participation throughout the Hackathon submission period. No additional usage benefits will be provided.
Complete and enter all of the required fields on the ôEnter a Submissionö page of the Hackathon Website (each a ôSubmissionö) during the Submission Period and follow the requirements below.
Project Requirements
What to Create:áEntrants must build a working software application that uses Kiro (vibe coding, agent hooks, steering docs, MCP, or specs) and submit it into one of the following categories (each a ôProjectö).á
á
Categories:


Resurrection:áBring your favorite dead technology back to life. Reimagine obsolete tech with todayÆs innovations or solving tomorrow's problems.


Frankenstein:áStitch together a chimera of technologies into one app. Bring together seemingly incompatible elements to build something unexpectedly powerful.


Skeleton Crew:áBuild a skeleton code template lean enough to be clear but flexible enough to support various use cases. Show us its versatility with two distinct applications from your foundation.


Costume Contest:áBuild any app but show us a haunting user interface thatÆs polished and unforgettable. Bring in spooky design elements that enhance your appÆs function.
á
Functionality:áThe Project must be capable of being successfully installed and running consistently on the platform for which it is intended and must function as depicted in the video and/or expressed in the text description.
Platforms:áA submitted Project must run on the platform for which it is intended and which is specified in the Submission Requirements.á
New & Existing:áProjects must be either newly created by the Entrant or, if the EntrantÆs Project existed prior to the Hackathon Submission Period, must have been significantly updated and must solve for a new use case after the start of the Hackathon Submission Period. Entrants should explain how their Project was significantly updated and what new use case it solves for during the Submission Period.
Third Party Integrations:áIf a Project integrates any third-party SDK, APIs and/or data, Entrant must be authorized to use them in accordance with any terms and conditions or licensing requirements of the tool.
á
Submission Requirementsá
Submissions to the Hackathon must meet the following requirements:
Include a Project built with the required developer tools and meets the above Project Requirements.
Include a text description that should explain the features and functionality of your Project.
Include a demonstration video of your Project. The video portion of the Submission:
should be less than three (3) minutes. Judges are not required to watch beyond three minutesá
should include footage that shows the Project functioning on the device for which it was built
must be uploaded to and made publicly visible on YouTube, Vimeo, Facebook Video, or Youku, and a link to the video must be provided on the submission form on the Hackathon Website; and
must not include third party trademarks, or copyrighted music or other material unless the Entrant has permission to use such material.
Provide a URL to your open source code repository for judging and testing.á
The repository must contain all necessary source code, assets, and instructions required for the project to be functional. The repository must be public and open source by including an open source license file. This license should be detectable and visible at the top of the repository page (in the About section).
The code repository must be public with an approvedáOSI Open Source License
Here are some instructions fromáGithubáon how to add it
Your repo must contain the /.kiro directory at the root of the project to show usage of specs, hooks, and steering. Do NOT add the /.kiro directory or sub-folders to your .gitignore, as this could disqualify your submission.
For Skeleton Crew projects only:áYour repo must contain 2 separate repo folders for the 2 separate applications.
Identify which category and bonus category you are submitting into.
Provide a write up on how Kiro was used. Judges must understand how effectively you used Kiro to develop your project. Show us your next-level understanding of Kiro features, e.g.:
Vibe coding:áHow did you structure your conversations with Kiro to build your project? What was the most impressive code generation Kiro helped you with?
Agent hooks:áWhat specific workflows did you automate with Kiro hooks? How did these hooks improve your development process?
Spec-driven development:áHow did you structure your spec for Kiro to implement? How did the spec-driven approach improve your development process? How did this compare to vibe coding?
Steering docs:áHow did you leverage steering to improve KiroÆs responses? Was there a particular strategy that made the biggest difference?
MCP:áHow did extending KiroÆs capabilities help you build your project? What sort of features or workflow improvements did MCP enable that otherwise would have been difficult or impossible?
á
Multiple Submissionsá
An Entrant may submit more than one Submission, however, each Submission must be unique and substantially different from each of the EntrantÆs other Submissions, as determined by the Sponsor and Devpost in their sole discretion.
Submission ownership
Be the original work of the Entrant, be solely owned by the Entrant, and not violate the IP rights of any other person or entity.
á
Testingá
Access must be provided to an EntrantÆs working Project for judging and testing by providing a link to a website, functioning demo, or a test build. If EntrantÆs website is private, Entrant must include login credentials in its testing instructions. The Entrant must make the Project available free of charge and without any restriction, for testing, evaluation and use by the Sponsor, Administrator and Judges until the Judging Period ends. Judges are not required to test the Project and may choose to judge based solely on the text description, images, and video provided in the Submission.
If the Project includes software that runs on proprietary or third party hardware that is not widely available to the public, including software running on devices or wearable technology other than smartphones, tablets, or desktop computers, the Sponsor and/or Administrator reserve the right, at their sole discretion, to require the Entrant to provide physical access to the Project hardware upon request.áá
Language Requirements
All Submission materials must be in English or, if not in English, the Entrant must provide an English translation of the demonstration video, text description, and testing instructions as well as all other materials submitted.á
Team Representation
If a team or organization is entering the Hackathon, they must appoint and authorize one individual (the ôRepresentativeö) to represent, act, and enter a Submission, on their behalf. The Representative must meet the eligibility requirements above. By entering a Submission on the Hackathon Website on behalf of a team or organization you represent and warrant that you are the Representative authorized to act on behalf of your team or organization.
Intellectual Propertyá
Your Submission must: (a) be your (or your Team, or OrganizationÆs) original work product; (b) be solely owned by you, your Team, your Organization with no other person or entity having any right or interest in it; and (c) not violate the intellectual property rights or other rights including but not limited to copyright, trademark, patent, contract, and/or privacy rights, of any other person or entity. An Entrant may contract with a third party for technical assistance to create the Submission provided the Submission components are solely the EntrantÆs work product and the result of the EntrantÆs ideas and creativity, and the Entrant owns all rights to them. An Entrant may submit a Submission that includes the use of open source software or hardware, provided the Entrant complies with applicable open source licenses and, as part of the Submission, creates software that enhances and builds upon the features and functionality included in the underlying open source product. By entering the Hackathon, you represent, warrant, and agree that your Submission meets these requirements.
Financial or Preferential Supportá
A Project must not have been developed, or derived from a Project developed, with financial or preferential support from the Sponsor or Administrator. Such Projects include, but are not limited to, those that received funding or investment for their development, were developed under contract, or received a commercial license, from the Sponsor or Administrator any time prior to the end of Hackathon Submission Period. The Sponsor, at their sole discretion, may disqualify a Project, if awarding a prize to the Project would create a real or apparent conflict of interest.
á
5. Submission Modifications
Draft Submissionsá
Prior to the end of the Submission Period, you may save draft versions of your submission on Devpost to your portfolio before submitting the Submission materials to the Hackathon for evaluation. Once the Submission Period has ended, you may not make any changes or alterations to your Submission, but you may continue to update the Project in your Devpost portfolio.
Modifications
After the Submission Period. The Sponsor and Devpost may permit you to modify part of your Submission after the Submission Period for the purpose of adding, removing or replacing material that potentially infringes a third party mark or right, discloses personally identifiable information, or is otherwise inappropriate. The modified Submission must remain substantively the same as the original Submission with the only modification being what the Sponsor and Devpost permits.á
á
6. Judges & Criteria
Eligible submissions will be evaluated by a panel of judges selected by the Sponsor (the ôJudgesö). Judges may be employees of the sponsor or third parties, may or may not be listed individually on the Hackathon Website, and may change before or during the Judging Period. Judging may take place in one or more rounds with one or more panels of Judges, at the discretion of the sponsor.á
Stage One)áThe first stage will determine via pass/fail whether the ideas meet a baseline level of viability, in that the Project reasonably fits the theme and reasonably applies the required APIs/SDKs featured in the Hackathon.
Stage Two)áAll Submissions that pass Stage One will be evaluated in Stage Two based on the following equally weighted criteria (the ôJudging Criteriaö):
Entries will be judged on the following equally weighted criteria, and according to the sole and absolute discretion of the judges:
Potential Value
Includes the extent to which the solution can be widely useful, easy to use, accessible, etc. Examples of considerations could include:
How unique or saturated the market is with these kinds of applications/solutions
Whether the UI is intuitive and brings the app functionality to the next level
If there is a clear need, extensibility, or other type of scalability of the Project


Implementation
Includes how well the idea is leveraging Kiro. Judges must understand how effectively Kiro was used to develop the project. Examples of effective usage include but are not limited to:
The variety of Kiro features/capabilities impactful in project development
The depth of understanding or benefit gained from a given Kiro feature/capability
The amount of experimentation and strategic decisions made in how Kiro features/capabilities are brought into the individualÆs development workflow.



Quality and Design
Includes creativity, originality, and polished design of the project, such as:á
Finding and using unique public resources like datasets
Solving a challenge in a unique way
Building in delightful UI experiences or other thoughtful choices
á
The scores from the Judges will determine the potential winners of the applicable prizes. The Entrant(s) that are eligible for a Prize, and whose Submissions earn the highest overall scores based on the applicable Judging Criteria, will become potential winners of that Prize.The Judges also have discretion to award up to 2 additional discretionary Influencer Judges Choice prizes based on the same criteria.
Tie Breakingá
For each Prize listed below, if two or more Submissions are tied, the tied Submission with the highest score in the first applicable criterion listed above will be considered the higher scoring Submission. In the event any ties remain, this process will be repeated, as needed, by comparing the tied SubmissionsÆ scores on the next applicable criterion. If two or more Submissions are tied on all applicable criteria, the panel of Judges will vote on the tied Submissions.
How to Enter Social Blitz Prize
Enter by posting on social (X, LI, IG, or BlueSky) your favorite thing about Kiro with a description of how it changed the way you approached development. To be considered, you must post during the submission period, tag @kirodotdev in your post, and use the hashtag #hookedonkiro. Sponsor will review submissions and select our favorite five. Sponsor reserves the right to choose any five posts as the winners.
How to Enter Bonus Blog Prize
Enter by submitting your blog post on https://dev.to/kirodotdev -- Use the hashtag #kiro when posting on the dev.to space.
How to Enter Best Startup Project
Enter by selecting the Startup Project category, confirm that you are a founder of the startup, and include your LinkedIn profile and startup website. Sponsor will review submissions and reserves the right to determine eligibility based on submitted details. Sponsor reserves the right to choose the winning project.
á
7. Intellectual Property Rights
All Submissions remain the intellectual property of the individuals or organizations that developed them. By submitting an entry, entrants agree that the Sponsor will have a fully paid, non-exclusive license to use such entry for judging the entry. Entrants agree that the sponsor and Devpost shall have the right to promote the Submission and use the name, likeness, voice and image of all individuals contributing to a Submission, in any materials promoting or publicizing the Hackathon and its results, during the Hackathon Period and for three years thereafter.á Some Submission components may be displayed to the public. Other Submission materials may be viewed by the sponsor, Devpost, and judges for screening and evaluation. By submitting an entry or accepting any prize, entrants represent and warrant that (a) submitted content is not copyrighted, protected by trade secret or otherwise subject to third party intellectual property rights or other proprietary rights, including privacy and publicity rights, unless entrant is the owner of such rights or has permission from their rightful owner to post the content; and (b) the content submitted does not contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, spyware or other disabling devices or harmful or malicious code.
á
8. Prizes
á
á
IMPORTANT NOTES ON MULTIPLE PRIZE ELIGIBILITY:
An eligible project can win one (1) Overall Prize AND up to two (2) Post Prizes OR one (1) Category Prize AND one (1) Bonus Prize AND up to two (2) Post Prizes.á
á
Substitutions & Changes:áPrizes are non-transferable by the winner. Sponsor in its sole discretion has the right to make a prize substitution of equivalent or greater value. Sponsor will not award a prize if there are no eligible Submissions entered in the Hackathon, or if there are no eligible Entrants or Submissions for a specific prize.
Verification Requirement:áTHE AWARD OF A PRIZE TO A POTENTIAL WINNER IS SUBJECT TO VERIFICATION OF THE IDENTITY, QUALIFICATIONS AND ROLE OF THE POTENTIAL WINNER IN THE CREATION OF THE SUBMISSION. No Submission or Entrant shall be deemed a winning Submission or winner until their post-competition prize affidavits have been completed and verified, even if prospective winners have been announced verbally or on the competition website. The final decision to designate a winner shall be made by the Sponsor and/or Administrator.á
Prize Delivery:áPrizes will be payable to the Entrant, if an individual; to the EntrantÆs Representative, if a Team; or to the Organization, if the Entrant is an Organization. It will be the responsibility of the winning EntrantÆs Representative to allocate the Prize among their Team or OrganizationÆs participating members, as the Representative deems appropriate. A monetary Prize will be mailed to the winning EntrantÆs address (if an individual) or the RepresentativeÆs address (if a Team or Organization), or sent electronically to the Entrant, EntrantÆs Representative, or OrganizationÆs bank account, only after receipt of the completed winner affidavit and other required forms (collectively the ôRequired Formsö), if applicable.áThe deadline for returning the Required Forms to the Administrator is ten (10) business days after the Required Forms are sent. Failure to provide correct information on the Required Forms, or other correct information required for the delivery of a Prize, may result in delayed Prize delivery, disqualification of the Entrant, or forfeiture of a Prize. Prizes will be delivered within 60 days of the Sponsor or DevpostÆs receipt of the completed Required Forms.
Fees & Taxes:áWinners (and in the case of Team or Organization, all participating members) are responsible for any fees associated with receiving or using a prize, including but not limited to, wiring fees or currency exchange fees. Winners (and in the case of Team or Organization, all participating members) are responsible for reporting and paying all applicable taxes in their jurisdiction of residence (federal, state/provincial/territorial and local). Winners may be required to provide certain information to facilitate receipt of the award, including completing and submitting any tax or other forms necessary for compliance with applicable withholding and reporting requirements. United States residents may be required to provide a completed form W-9 and residents of other countries may be required to provide a completed W-8BEN form. Winners are also responsible for complying with foreign exchange and banking regulations in their respective jurisdictions and reporting the receipt of the Prize to relevant government departments/agencies, if necessary. The Sponsor, Devpost, and/or Prize provider reserves the right to withhold a portion of the prize amount to comply with the tax laws of the United States or other Sponsor jurisdiction, or those of a winnerÆs jurisdiction.
á
9. Entry Conditions and Release
By entering the Hackathon, you (and, if you are entering on behalf of a Team, Organization each participating members) agree(s) to the following:
The relationship between you, the Entrant, and the Sponsor and Administrator, is not a confidential, fiduciary, or other special relationship.
You will be bound by and comply with these Official Rules and the decisions of the Sponsor, Administrator, and/or the Hackathon Judges which are binding and final in all matters relating to the Hackathon.
You release, indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Promotion Entities, and their respective parent, subsidiary, and affiliated companies, the Prize suppliers and any other organizations responsible for sponsoring, fulfilling, administering, advertising or promoting the Hackathon, and all of their respective past and present officers, directors, employees, agents and representatives (hereafter the ôReleased Partiesö) from and against any and all claims, expenses, and liabilities (including reasonable attorneysÆ fees), including but not limited to negligence and damages of any kind to persons and property, defamation, slander, libel, violation of right of publicity, infringement of trademark, copyright or other intellectual property rights, property damage, or death or personal injury arising out of or relating to a EntrantÆs entry, creation of Submission or entry of a Submission, participation in the Hackathon, acceptance or use or misuse of the Prize (including any travel or activity related thereto) and/or the broadcast, transmission, performance, exploitation or use of the Submission as authorized or licensed by these Official Rules.á
Without limiting the foregoing, the Released Parties shall have no liability in connection with:á
Any incorrect or inaccurate information, whether caused by the Sponsor or AdministratorÆs electronic or printing error, or by any of the equipment or programming associated with or utilized in the Hackathon;á
Technical failures of any kind, including, but not limited to malfunctions, interruptions, or disconnections in phone lines, internet connectivity or electronic transmission errors, or network hardware or software or failure of the Hackathon Website;
Unauthorized human intervention in any part of the entry process or the Hackathon;á
Technical or human error which may occur in the administration of the Hackathon or the processing of Submissions; orá
Any injury or damage to persons or property which may be caused, directly or indirectly, in whole or in part, from the EntrantÆs participation in the Hackathon or receipt or use or misuse of any Prize.
The Released Parties are not responsible for incomplete, late, misdirected, damaged, lost, illegible, or incomprehensible Submissions or for address or email address changes of the Entrants. Proof of sending or submitting the aforementioned will not be deemed to be proof of receipt by the Sponsor or Administrator. If for any reason any EntrantÆs Submission is determined to have not been received or been erroneously deleted, lost, or otherwise destroyed or corrupted, the EntrantÆs sole remedy is to request the opportunity to resubmit its Submission. Such a request must be made promptly after the Entrant knows or should have known there was a problem and will be determined at the sole discretion of the Sponsor.
á
10. Publicity
By participating in the Hackathon, Entrant consents to the promotion and display of the EntrantÆs Submission, and to the use of personal information about themselves for promotional purposes, by the Sponsor, Administrator, and third parties acting on their behalf. Such personal information includes, but is not limited to, your name, likeness, photograph, voice, opinions, comments and hometown and country of residence. It may be used in any existing or newly created media, worldwide without further payment or consideration or right of review, unless prohibited by law. Authorized use includes but is not limited to advertising and promotional purposes.á
á
11. General Conditionsá
Sponsor and Administrator reserve the right, in their sole discretion, to cancel, suspend and/or modify the Hackathon, or any part of it, in the event of a technical failure, fraud, or any other factor or event that was not anticipated or is not within their control.
Sponsor and Administrator reserve the right in their sole discretion to disqualify any individual or Entrant if it finds to be actually or presenting the appearance of tampering with the entry process or the operation of the Hackathon or to be acting in violation of these Official Rules or in a manner that is inappropriate, unsportsmanlike, not in the best interests of this Hackathon, or a violation of any applicable law or regulation.
Any attempt by any person to undermine the proper conduct of the Hackathon may be a violation of criminal and civil law. Should the Sponsor or Administrator suspect that such an attempt has been made or is threatened, they reserve the right to take appropriate action including but not limited to requiring an Entrant to cooperate with an investigation and referral to criminal and civil law enforcement authorities.
If there is any discrepancy or inconsistency between the terms and conditions of the Official Rules and disclosures or other statements contained in any Hackathon materials, including but not limited to the Hackathon Submission form, Hackathon Website, or advertising, the terms and conditions of the Official Rules shall prevail.
The terms and conditions of the Official Rules are subject to change at any time, including the rights or obligations of the Entrant, the Sponsor and Administrator. The Sponsor and Administrator will post the terms and conditions of the amended Official Rules on the Hackathon Website. To the fullest extent permitted by law, any amendment will become effective at the time specified in the posting of the amended Official Rules or, if no time is specified, the time of posting.
If at any time prior to the deadline, an Entrant or prospective Entrant believes that any term in the Official Rules is or may be ambiguous, they must submit a written request for clarification.á
The Sponsor or AdministratorÆs failure to enforce any term of these Official Rules shall not constitute a waiver of that provision. Should any provision of these Official Rules be or become illegal or unenforceable in any jurisdiction whose laws or regulations may apply to an Entrant, such illegality or unenforceability shall leave the remainder of these Official Rules, including the Rule affected, to the fullest extent permitted by law, unaffected and valid. The illegal or unenforceable provision shall be replaced by a valid and enforceable provision that comes closest and best reflects the SponsorÆs intention in a legal and enforceable manner with respect to the invalid or unenforceable provision.
Excluding Submissions, all intellectual property related to this Hackathon, including but not limited to copyrighted material, trademarks, trade-names, logos, designs, promotional materials, web pages, source codes, drawings, illustrations, slogans and representations are owned or used under license by the Sponsor and/or Administrator. All rights are reserved. Unauthorized copying or use of any copyrighted material or intellectual property without the express written consent of its owners is strictly prohibited. Any use in a Submission of Sponsor or AdministratorÆs intellectual property shall be solely to the extent provided for in these Official Rules.
á
12. Limitations of Liability
By entering, all Entrants (including, in the case of a Team or Organization, all participating members) agree to release the Released Parties from any and all liability in connection with the Prizes or EntrantÆs participation in the Hackathon. Provided, however, that any liability limitation regarding gross negligence or intentional acts, or events of death or body injury shall not be applicable in jurisdictions where such limitation is not legal.
á
13. Disputes
Except where prohibited by law, as a condition of participating in this Hackathon, Entrant agrees that:
Any and all disputes and causes of action arising out of or connected with this Hackathon, or any Prizes awarded, shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action lawsuit, and exclusively by final and binding arbitration under the rules of the American Arbitration Association and held at the AAA regional office nearest the contestant;
The Federal Arbitration Act shall govern the interpretation, enforcement and all proceedings at such arbitration; and
Judgment upon such arbitration award may be entered in any court having jurisdiction.
Under no circumstances will Entrant be permitted to obtain awards for, and Entrant hereby waives all rights to claim, punitive, incidental or consequential damages, or any other damages, including attorneysÆ fees, other than contestantÆs actual out-of-pocket expenses (i.e., costs associated with entering this Hackathon), and Entrant further waives all rights to have damages multiplied or increased.
All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules, or the rights and obligations of the Entrant and Sponsor in connection with this Hackathon, shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the substantive laws of the State of New York, USA without regard to New York choice of law rules.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
á
14. Additional Terms
Please review the Devpost Terms of Service atáhttps://info.devpost.com/termsáfor additional rules that apply to your participation in the Hackathon and more generally your use of the Hackathon Website. Such Terms of Service are incorporated by reference into these Official Rules, including that the term "Poster" in the Terms of Service shall mean the same as "Sponsor" in these Official Rules." If there is a conflict between the Terms of Service and these Official Rules, these Official Rules shall control with respect to this Hackathon only.
á
15. EntrantÆs Personal Information
Information collected from Entrants is subject to DevpostÆs Privacy Policy, which is available atáhttps://info.devpost.com/privacy.
For questions, send an email to support@devpost.com.

